Java的接口是一种有用的语言机制
Java's interface is a useful language mechanism
用于表示抽象数据类型。
for expressing an abstract data type.
Java中的接口只是方法签名列表，
An Interface in Java is just a list of method signatures,
没有方法体。
no method bodies.
然后类实现一个接口
And then a class implements an interface
如果它在implements子句中声明接口
if it declares the interface in its implements clause
在类声明的顶部
at the top of the class declaration
并提供了所有缺少的方法体
and provides the method bodies that were missing for all
接口方法的。
of the interfaces methods.
所以在Java中考虑抽象数据类型的一种方法
So one way to think about an abstract data type in Java
它是一个接口，因为它完全定义了
is that it's an interface because it's defined entirely
通过它的运作。
by its operations.
然后它的实现是一个类
And then its implementation is a class
实现那个接口的。
that implements that interface.
现在，这种方法的一大优点是
Now, one of the big advantages of this approach
接口指定了客户端的契约
is that the interface specifies the contract for the client
再也没有了。
and nothing more.
接口是客户机程序员所需要的
The interface is all that a client programmer needs
阅读理解ADT。
to read to understand the ADT.
客户端无法创建意外依赖项
The client can't create inadvertent dependencies
因为实例变量不能
on the ADT's rep because instance variables can't
完全被放在一个接口中。
be put in an interface at all.
你没有代表。
You don't have a rep.
执行情况得到了很好的保证
The implementation is kept well and truly
完全分居在不同的阶级中。
separated in a different class altogether.
另一个优点是
Another advantage is that multiple different
抽象数据类型的表示
representations of the abstract data type
可以与不同的类在同一程序中共存
can coexist in the same program as different classes
实现相同的接口。
implementing the same interface.
当抽象数据类型仅表示为
When an abstract data type is represented just
作为一个没有接口的类，
as a single class without an interface,
很难有多个代表。
it's harder to have multiple representations.
所以在前面阅读的MyString示例中，
So in the MyString example from the earlier reading,
MyString只是一个类。
MyString was just a single class.
我们研究了MyString的两种不同表示，
We explored two different representations for MyString,
但我们不能在ADT中同时使用这两种表示
but we couldn't use both representations for the ADT
在同一个程序中。
in the same program.
Java静态类型检查允许编译器
Java Static type checking allows the compiler
在执行ADT合同时发现许多错误。
to catch many mistakes in implementing an ADT's contract.
例如，这是一个编译时错误
For instance, it's a compile time error
省略所需的方法之一
to omit one of the required methods
或者给一个方法错误的返回类型。
or to give a method the wrong return type.
不幸的是，编译器没有检查我们
Unfortunately, the compiler doesn't check for us
代码遵循那些方法的规范
that the code adheres to the specs of those methods that
都写在文档注释中。
are written in the documentation comments.